newspunch.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy - News Punch

[ **Please Note** : This privacy policy was last updated on May 23, 2018 and is subject to future change without notice.]

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to YourNewsWire.com and The People’s Voice, Inc and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to The People’s Voice, Inc include YourNewsWire.com and The People’s Voice. The People’s Voice website is a breaking news, entertainment, and politics site. By using the The People’s Voice website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**  
The People’s Voice may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. The People’s Voice may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, household income and political affiliation. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by The People’s Voice. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the The People’s Voice website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through The People’s Voice’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

The People’s Voice encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from The People’s Voice so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. The People’s Voice is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the The People’s Voice website.

**Use of your Personal Information**  
The People’s Voice collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

The People’s Voice uses personally identifiable information collected from you for the following general purposes:

  * To customize the advertising and content you see;
  * To improve the design and content of our site;
  * To enter you in editorial contributions or promotions at your specific request;
  * To provide you with customer service.

The People’s Voice may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from The People’s Voice and its affiliates. The People’s Voice may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

The People’s Voice does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

The People’s Voice may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. The People’s Voice may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to The People’s Voice, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

The People’s Voice may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within The People’s Voice, in order to determine what The People’s Voice services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within The People’s Voice to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

The People’s Voice will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on The People’s Voice or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of The People’s Voice; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of The People’s Voice, or the public.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
The People’s Voice will not sell, share or otherwise disclose any personally identifiable information about our current or former web site users to third party companies or individuals, except as permitted or required by law.

The People’s Voice may share or disclose personally identifiable information about you to other companies or individuals when:

  * We have your consent to share the information;
  * We utilize third party service providers to provide products, services or functions on our behalf (such as sending emails or processing credit cards), and require these service providers to agree to maintain the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information and not to use your personally identifiable information for any reason except to carry out the purpose(s) for which we hired them;
  * We need to protect our legal rights (for example, if we are trying to collect money you owe us or we are trying to enforce our [Terms of Use](https://newspunch.com/website-terms-of-use/) or other agreement with you);

Aggregate information is information that we (or third party service providers on our behalf) collect about yournewswire.com Web site users on an anonymous basis. We may share aggregate demographic and usage information with our prospective and actual business partners, advertisers and other third parties.

**Cookies**  
The People’s Voice (or third party service providers on our behalf) may set and access cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data (often including a unique identifier), that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Yournewswire.com uses cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to identify you as a registered user, personalize your experience at our site, save your password in password-protected areas, and display relevant content, products, services and advertising.

To the extent that The People’s Voice utilizes third party service providers to set and access cookies on the computer of our Web site users on behalf of The People’s Voice, we require such service providers to agree to maintain the confidentiality of the information collected and not to use such information for any reason except to carry out the purpose(s) for which we hired them.

We use reputable third parties to present or serve some or all of the advertisements on our Web site. These third party network advertisers may set and access their own cookies on your computer. The use of cookies by third parties is subject to such third party’s own privacy policies.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to reject cookies. If you set your browser to reject cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of certain features offered through our Web site.

If you would like more information about the information collection practices of a particular third-party advertising service provider, or if you would like more information on how to opt out of a third-party advertising service provider’s information collection practices, go to [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/), or for apps, at <http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices>.

Additionally, some of our third-party advertising service providers are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). You can obtain more information about these third-party advertising service providers’ information collection practices, and opt out of such practices (and at the same time opt out of the collection practices of other, or all, NAI members) by following the opt out instructions on the NAI’s website at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Please note that one of our third-party advertising service providers is DoubleClick. You can opt out of the use of cookies by DoubleClick by visiting <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>.

**Security of your Personal Information**  
The People’s Voice secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

**Children Under Thirteen**  
The People’s Voice does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe **  
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from The People’s Voice by contacting us here:  
– Web page: <https://newspunch.com/contact/>  
– Email: [contact@yournewswire.com](mailto:contact@yournewswire.com)  
– Phone: (424) 666-1274

**Changes to this Statement**  
The People’s Voice will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. The People’s Voice encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how The People’s Voice is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**  
The People’s Voice welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that The People’s Voice has not adhered to this Statement, please contact The People’s Voice at:

The People’s Voice, Inc  
137 N. Larchmont Blvd  
Suite 118  
Los Angeles  
CA 90004

Email Address:  
contact@yournewswire.com

Telephone number:  
(424) 666-1274

_Effective as of May 23, 2018_
